Previously on "desperate housewives"...
在此前的“欲乱绝情妻”中...
Zach's gone from silvercrest.
Zach离开了silvercrest康复中心
hungry?
饿吗？
Sometimes...
有时候...
If I don't get some help, I will lose my mind.
如果我得不到一些帮助，我就无法自制了
Where can I score some high-grade nanny?
我能从哪儿找到高水准的保姆？
No matter how hard you try...
无论你如何努力...
FBI. Open the door.
联邦调查局。开门
Carlos Solis, I have a warrant for your arrest.
Carlos Solis,你被捕了
Some problems...
有些问题...
I-I'm sorry. And you are?
不好意思，请问你是？
Maisy does love to rule her little kingdom.
Maisy热衷于统治她的那个小小的王国
You are unhappy with our sex life.
你对我们的性生活不满意
You're not getting something from me, but you're simply too afraid to ask.
尽管你没能从我这里得到些什么， 但你就是不敢提出来
Can't be easily solved.
难以轻易解决
To understand Maisy Gibbons,
要了解Maisy Gibbons，
you first need to know how she spent her afternoons.
你首先需要知道她如何度过她的下午
Her mornings were spent running errands for her husband.
她上午为她的丈夫跑腿办事
Hi.
嗨
Her evenings were spent washing dishes and helping with homework.
晚上则洗碗和帮助女儿做功课
Um, okay, so 9 plus 1 is...
嗯，好，那么9加1是...
but her afternoons
但在下午的时候
-
well, they were spent in the company of men.
她和男人们在一起
Frustrated...
那些沮丧的...
misunderstood...
被误解的...
lonely men willing to pay money to feel a little less lonely.
孤独的但愿意花钱 使自己变得不那么孤独的男人们
And Maisy Gibbons was willing to help them.
而Maisy Gibbons愿意帮助他们
Maisy, I've always wondered,
Maisy,我一直觉得很惊讶，
nobody knows about your little hobby, do they?
没有人知道你这个小小的爱好，对吧？
Mnh-mnh.
是啊
Is it hard keeping a secret like this?
要保守这样的一个秘密是不是很难？
Well, maybe if it was just my secret,
如果这只是我一个人的秘密，也许很难
but the way I see it, I keep the secrets of every man who comes to me,
但从我的观点看，我在保守那些 来找我的男人们的秘密
and I find that absolutely exhilarating.
这样的话我就觉得非常兴奋
A few years back, Harold lost his job,
几年前，Harold没了工作，
and we had to give up our membership at the country club.
所以我们必须去注销 我们在乡间俱乐部的会员资格
And then one day, one of my club friends asked why she hadn't seen me around lately,
然后有一天，我在俱乐部的一个朋友问我 为什么最近没去俱乐部
and I told her that we couldn't afford it anymore.
我告诉她我们支付不起俱乐部费用了
She waved it off like it was nothing,
她摆了摆手好像这根本无关紧要，
but I saw her get that look in her eye, that look of pity.
但我看到了她的眼神，那种觉得我可怜的眼神
Maybe she was just trying to be nice.
也许她仅仅是想表现得像个好心人
Anyway, is that so bad,
不管怎样，难道为别人难过
feeling sorry for someone?
是那么坏的一件事吗？
Well, when they say something, they are being supportive,
当人们说那些话的时候，他们是支持你的，
but when they say nothing,
但当他们什么都没说的时候，
it's because they think that you're so far gone, you're never coming back.
那是因为他们认为 你已经没有可能东山再起了
Gotcha.
明白了
Anyway, a couple of months later,
不管怎样，几个月后，
I started my little hobby,
I started my little hobby, 我开始了我的小小爱好，
and the most wonderful thing happened.
然后最奇妙的事情发生了
This woman's husband became one of my regulars.
这个女人的丈夫成为了我的常客
Wow.
喔
Oh.
哦
Would you be a lamb and go out the back?
你能听话地从后门出去吗？
It's my next appointment.
我的下一个预约客户来了
Sure.
当然
It's the husband of the woman I was telling you about.
是那个我刚才正跟你说到的 女人的丈夫
Hello there.
你好啊
Hey, Maisy.
你好，Maisy
Episode 10 : Come Back to Me
第十集 : 回到我身边
Every morality play has its cast of characters.
每一场道德戏都有自己的角色设定:
There is always an innocent victim,
总是有一个无辜的被害者，
a deceitful villain,
一个撒谎的坏家伙，
a prosecutor who seeks the truth,
一个探究真相的检察官，
a magistrate who dispenses justice,
一个主持正义的地方法官，
and a lawyer who charges too much.
和一个收费过高的律师
This morality play was being produced at the fairview county courthouse.
这一场道德戏在fairview地方法院上演
Its themes were trust and betrayal.
主题是信任与背叛
So what's your issue with bail in this case, Ms. Mcready?
Mcready小姐，在本案中你对保释有何意见？
We want bail denied, your honor.
法官大人，控方希望不批准保释
The defendant's company imported goods manufactured by slave labor,
被告的公司进口的是经由奴役工人而生产的商品，
and his business partner Mr. Tanaka has already fled the country,
被告的生意伙伴田中先生已经潜逃出国，
and Mr. Solis himself has refused to surrender his passport.
而Solis先生不愿意上交他的护照
Dog ate your client's passport, Mr. Hartley?
Hartley先生，你客户的护照被狗吃了吗？
It's been temporarily misplaced, your honor,
法官大人，护照放错地方了，暂时找不到，
but we maintain that Kisho Tanaka set up and executed the entire operation.
但我们认为是田中设计并操作了整件事
Mr. Solis is no business partner, but merely a hired contractor.
Solis先生不是生意合伙人，而仅仅是一个雇员
And I'd also like to point out that my client is the sole provider
并且我想指出我的客户是他的妻子
for his wife and his mother, who is hospitalized in a coma as we speak.
和他目前正昏迷住院的母亲 经济收入的唯一来源
Bring me the passport, and Mr. Solis can visit his mother.
把护照交给我，Solis就可以去探望他的母亲了
Until then, your client is denied bail and remanded.
但在此之前，你客户的保释请求被驳回并送还监禁
What's next?
下一个案子？
You better finish those brussels sprouts.
你们最好吃掉这些芽甘蓝
And don't think I can't see them hidden under your macaroni.
别以为我没看到你们把它们藏在通心粉下面
I hate brussels sprouts.
我讨厌芽甘蓝
Yeah, well, brussels sprouts help you grow.
是啊，但是芽甘蓝有助于你们成长
You don't want to be short your whole life, do you?
你们不想一辈子做个矮子吧？
Here, look, you know what we'll do?
看，你们知道该怎么吃吗？
We're going to dip them in a little cheese.
把他们在奶酪里蘸一下
Here you go.
可以了
Good. Yummy. Yummy.
好的，好吃哦，好吃哦
- Ew!
- 呕!
Yuck!
恶!
Fine, fine, be 3'8" the rest of your life.
好，好，你们一辈子都3英尺8英寸高吧
See if I care.
我才不管呢
Good luck finding girlfriends.
祝你们能找到女朋友
Hey, didn't you have a lunch today?
嗨，你不是有一个午餐约定吗？
I'm going to cancel it.
我要取消它
The boys are in rare form, and you're still finding your way.
这些男孩子今天出奇地不听话， 再说你也才刚刚入门
Lynette, it's been two days.
Lynette, 已经两天了
I don't want to shock them by suddenly disappearing. You know, deep down, they're very sensitive.
我不想因为我的突然消失而吓到他们，你知道， 其实在内心深处他们是很敏感的
They'll be fine.
他们会没事的
Now go.
走吧
Get out of here.
离开这儿
You have my cell phone number. You call me if you need anything.
你有我的手机号码， 有任何需要就打电话给我
I will.
我会的
O kay.
好的
1, 2, 3. Whoa! Get in, get in.
1, 2, 3. 噢! 靠紧点，靠紧点
- Mm, okay.
- 妈，好了
Bye.
拜拜
- Bye, mom!
- 拜拜，妈妈
Bye.
拜拜
Bye!
Okay.
好
Watch your hands.
当心手
Um, I'm going to eat upstairs. I've got a ton of homework.
嗯，我到楼上去吃 我有一堆的作业要做
What are you, storing up for winter?
你在干嘛？为冬天储存食物？
I'm just really hungry.
我只是真的很饿
Mm.
嗯
Oh, I talked to dad today, and apparently, he and Brandi might break up.
哦，我今天和爸爸谈了， 看上去他和Brandi可能要分手了
Oh. How awful.
噢，多糟啊
Mom, you're smiling.
妈，你在笑
Am I?
是吗？
Anyway, because of all the drama, he can't take me this weekend,
不管怎样，由于这个原因， 这个周末他不能来带我
so I'll be home after all. Good night.
所以我会待在这里，晚安
Oh, great. Our romantic weekend's off.
哦，“好”极了，我们的浪漫周末吹了
We could move it to my house.
我们可以在我家里进行
No.
不行
Why not?
为什么不？
I just
我只是想
- I just want it to be special.
- 我只是想使它特别一点
And it can't be special at my house.
而在我家就不能使它特别
Okay, I know this sounds weird, but I just need to have my things around me.
我知道这听起来很古怪，但我需要 我自己的东西在我的周围
What things?
什么东西？
Perfumes and oils, and I want to pick out the outfit that you're going to tear off me.
香水和油，并且我想选出那种你会想 把它从我身上扯下来的小东东
And plus, I need to be in complete control of the lighting.
另外，我需要对灯光的完全控制
Okay.
好的
We'll wait till next weekend.
我们等到下周末吧
You are just the sweetest guy.
你真是最好的男人
All right. I can't wait till next weekend.
好吧，我等不到下周末了
No, me neither.
我也不能
What about tomorrow while Julie's at school? I've got an early job, and that's it.
要不明天吧？Julie在学校， 我早点把活干完，那就好了
Oh, no good. My publisher's got me under the gun for something. What about friday?
噢，不行，我的出版商催得很急 星期五怎么样？
I'm repiping a house.
我要为一个房子重新铺管子
Mm, damn karl.
嗯，该死的Karl
I can't hide you in my room forever, and...
我不能一直都把你藏在我的房间里
I think we need to tell my mom.
我想我们应该告诉我妈妈
You can trust her, I promise.
你可以信任她，我保证
You didn't tell her what I told you, did you?
你没有告诉她我告诉你的事吧？
No. No, no, no. I would never tell anyone that.
没有，没有，没有，没有，我谁都不会说
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I don't want to cause problems for you.
我不想替你添麻烦
I'm just
我只是
- I'm just going to go.
- 我只是要走了
Zach, stop. Don't go.
Zach, 停下，不要走
I won't tell her.
我不会告诉她的
I swear, I'll be out of here soon.
我发誓我很快就会离开这里
I'll think of something, okay?
我会想办法，好吗？
Hello.
Hello
Why are you up?
你为什么没睡？
I could ask you the same question.
我可以问你同样的问题
I'm going to bed.
我要睡了
I didn't ask you to wait up for me.
我并没要你等我
Remember, I'm here as our children's father, not your husband.
记住，我在这儿只是作为我们孩子的父亲， 而不是你的丈夫
What are you doing?
你在干嘛？
Were you with a woman?
你刚才和一个女人在一起？
Did you tell her that you have a wife, or does that hinder your pickup style?
你告诉过她你是有妇之夫吗？ 或者那样会影响你的艳遇？
All right.
好吧
Even if I was seeing someone, I have every right to.
就算我和别的女人有染，我也有充足的理由
Exploring options is the whole point of being separated.
分居的意义就在于能够寻求新的选择
"Options"? I'm not a mutual fund, Rex.
选择？Rex，我可不是一个共有基金
Oh, that's not
那不是
-
Bree, you should get out there.
Bree, 你应该主动出去
Try and meet someone.
试着寻找你的真爱
Meet someone.
寻找我的真爱
I'm raising your children.
我在养育你的孩子们
I am just trying to move on with my life.
我只是想渡过这一关，继续我的生活
It is nothing to be ashamed of.
这没什么可耻的
Oh, okay. I tell you what, then
好啊，我说
-
why don't you just call up your mystery woman and invite her over?
你为什么不干脆邀请你的那个神秘女人过来
I'll pull out the sofa bed, and you can take her right there.
我会整理好沙发床， 你们在那里就可以胡作非为了
Andrew, Danielle, daddy's going to fornicate for us!
Andrew, Danielle, 爸爸要在我们面前通奸了
Just keep your voice down.
小声一点
Why? Are you feeling ashamed?
为什么？你觉得可耻了？
The next morning started with a banging.
第二天的到来伴随着一阵猛烈的敲门声
No one knew where Martha Huber was, and Edie Britt was starting to worry.
没有人知道Martha Huber在哪里， Edie Britt开始担心了
Edie didn't like worrying. She felt it gave her wrinkles.
Edie不喜欢担心，她觉得这样会增加她的皱纹
So out of concern for her face and Mrs. Huber, Edie decided to find out what was going on.
所以出于对她的容貌和Huber夫人的担心， Edie决定查明到底发生了什么
Yao lin, listen to me.
Yao Lin, 听我说
It's very important that we find Carlos's passport.
我们必须要找到Carlos的护照，这很重要
I already looked through his office, so I need you to search the bedroom.
我已经找遍了他的办公室， 所以我想要你在卧室里找一下
What?
什么？
With Mr. Solis in jail, how are you going to pay me? I have children.
Solis先生入狱了，你怎么付我工资啊？ 我还有孩子要养呢
Yao lin, your kids are in their 20s.
Yao lin, 你的孩子们都20多岁了
If it'll make you shut up...
如果这能让你闭嘴...
h ere.
看
Three weeks in advance.
预支三个礼拜的工资
If you don't mind, can I call your bank?
你不介意的话，我能给你的银行打个电话吗？
Yao lin, don't be stupid. People don't become poor overnight.
Yao lin, 别犯傻 没有人一夜之间变穷的
That's my car. Oh, my god.
那是我的车，上帝啊
Hey!
嗨!
H ey!
What are you doing?
你在干什么啊？
Where are you taking my car?
你要把我的车弄到哪儿去？
Government's impounding it. Here's your receipt.
政府没收了，这是你的收据
Call that number if you have any questions.
如果有任何问题，打这个号码
You call this a paint job?
你这也算是油漆过了？
I don't want to see it again until it's perfect!
在它变得完美之前，别让我再看到它
Wonder what's going on over there.
我在想到底是怎么回事
I mean, Claire did okay with the kids yesterday, but that could have been beginner's luck.
我的意思是，Claire昨天和孩子们相处得很好， 但那可能是初学者的运气
You think I should call? I should call.
你认为我应该打个电话吗？我应该打一个
Lynette, for the first time in years, you finally have some free time,
Lynette, 在这么多年来你终于有了一些自由时间
and you're wasting it obsessing about the kids.
而你却把它浪费在担心你的孩子上
It's just I don't know this woman. I mean, not really.
关键是我不了解这个女人，我的意思是，不真正了解
So she has a degree in sociology. Well, big deal. Who doesn't?
她有社会学学位 那又怎么样，谁没有呢？
My boys are a lot to handle. What if she's not up to it?
我的孩子们很难管理 要是她搞不定怎么办？
You know, if you really have that many doubts, you should go buy a hidden camera.
我说，如果你真的有那么多的疑问， 你应该去买个隐藏的摄像器
What, a nanny-cam?
什么？一个保姆监视器？
Yeah.
是啊
People do terrible things when they think no one's watching them.
当人们认为没人在盯着他们的时候，他们就会做很不好的事情
Yeah.
是啊
I don't really think I could videotape Claire. It would be a breach of trust.
我觉得我不能监视Claire, 这是一种不信任
Trust is overrated.
别那么相信别人
So...how are things with you and Rex?
嗯...你和Rex现在怎么样？
Fine. Why do you ask?
很好，你为什么这么问？
Well, I'm just curious. I mean, he moves out, moves back in. Is he back for good?
我只是好奇。我的意思是，他搬出去， 又搬回来。他搬回来是出于好的原因吗？
Uh, the situation is, um, fluid.
嗯，情况有些，嗯，不稳定
I'm not certain what his plans are yet.
我不确定他到底怎么计划的
Huh.
哦
So if you're not sure he's back for good, why are you ironing his shirts?
那么如果你不确定他搬回来是出于好的原因， 为什么你还熨他的寸衫呢
Because I have faith that he'll come back
因为我相信他会回到我身边的
and that he'll do the right thing.
他会做正确的事
That's good.
那就好
It's good to have faith in people.
对别人有信心是一件好事
Yeah.
是啊
But I'd still buy that camera.
但我还是会买那个摄像器
Hello?
你好？
- Mike?
Yeah?
什么事？
My oven's out.
我的烤箱坏了
Mm-hmm.
嗯...
Come over and help me find my pilot light.
过来帮我找找我的标灯
Al green's "here I am (come and take me)"
Al Green's "here I am (come and take me)"
Laying all my troubles down
here I am, baby
come and take me
ooh, come and take me
take me by the hand
ooh, yeah, show me
here I am, baby
aah!
Oh, candles, candles.
哦，蜡烛，蜡烛
Here I am, baby
come and take me,
here I am, baby
come and take me
Take me by the hand
here I am, baby
Mike, is that you?
Mike, 是你吗？
I'm up here.
我在这儿
I can always call you
for a helpin' hand
I know you'll do the best you can
[Come on in...]
[进来吧...]
but it don't take much from me
Mike?
Oh, there's love inside me
I believe there's going to be an explosion
yeah, yeah, whoo-hoo
it's tough for me,
oh, yeah
Aah!
啊!
Oh, my god.
哦，上帝啊
What the hell?
怎么回事啊？
I'm so sorry. I thought there was someone in the house.
对不起，我以为有什么人在房子里
So you took your clothes off?
所以你脱掉了你的衣服？
No, my clothes were already off. I was going to seduce you.
不，我的衣服本来就是脱掉了的 我本想诱惑你
It didn't really work.
并不奏效
Oh, I'm sorry. Are you okay?
哦，对不起，你没事吧？
Well...
嗯...
please don't be mad.
请千万别生气
hey there.
你好啊
Zach.
Zach
What are you doing here?
你在这儿干嘛啊？
Later that day, while Claire was out getting the boys wired on ice cream,
就在那一天的晚些时候，当Claire带着孩子们 出门买冰淇淋，
Lynette did some wiring of her own.
Lynette自己安装了摄像器
No, you can't do this. You can't send Zach back.
不，你不能这么做，你不能把Zach送回去
Julie, what else can I do? He can't stay here.
Julie,我还能怎么做呢？他不能呆在这儿
His father sent him to a psycho ward.
他爸爸把他扔进了精神病院
Actually, they call it a rehabilitation center.
实际上，他们叫它康复中心
What do you think?
你怎么认为？
Paul is his father. He has a right to know his son's okay.
Paul是他的父亲，他有权知道他儿子平安无事
And if he finds out you're hiding him, you could get in a lot of trouble.
如果他发现你们藏着他，你们会有大麻烦
He's right.
他说得对
Sorry, guys.
对不起，各位
Mom, please don't do this.
妈妈，不要这样做
If you knew what Zach had been through
如果你知道Zach的遭遇
-
Julie, Julie, it's okay. I'll be fine.
Julie, Julie, 没关系，我会没事的
I'll, uh, take him back over so you two can...
我把他带回去，你们可以...
listen, if Paul sees Zach and freaks out
听着，如果Paul看到Zach后举止失常
-
I'll bring him right back.
我会把他带回来
Thank you.
谢谢
Young lady, we need to talk about what you did.
小姐，我们该谈谈你所做的事情
I really don't feel like talking to you right now.
我现在实在不想和你谈
Uh, listen, Zach...
嗯，听着，Zach...
if things ever get really bad...
如果事情变得很糟...
it's got my cell number on it.
这是我的手机号码
You give me a call... anytime.
你打给我...任何时候都可以
Thanks.
谢谢
Oh, thank god.
哦，感谢上帝
How did you
你怎么
-
we'll talk later.
我们以后谈
Remember, anytime.
记住，任何时候
I heard you moved back home.
我听说你搬回家住了
Yeah, I-I had to. We -- we had some problems with Andrew.
是啊，没办法。Andrew有一些问题
I'll move out eventually.
我总归会搬出来的
Spikes or pearls?
钉子还是珍珠？
Your choice.
你选吧
You know what I think?
你知道我怎么想？
Hmm?
嗯？
You don't really want to leave her.
你其实并不想离开她
Please don't psycho analyze me.
拜托别精神分析我
Well, you're still in love with her.
你依然爱她
I never said I wasn't.
我从来没说过我不爱她
Then why divorce?
那么为什么离婚？
Now you're rooting for us two crazy kids to work it out?
现在你又鼓励我和Bree重归与好了？
Hey
嗨!
You know me.
你了解我
I'm just a romantic at heart.
我只不过内心深处浪漫而已
Scarves or cuffs?
丝巾还是手铐？
Up to you.
随便你
Even if I could find a way to deal with Bree's whole obsessive-compulsive thing,
E即使我能找到个办法忍受Bree的偏执和强迫，
it's not the only problem in our marriage.
我们的婚姻里依然还有别的问题
As you know, I have certain needs.
你知道，我有一些特别的需要，
Boots or stilettos?
靴子还是细跟鞋？
Stilettos... please.
细跟鞋...拜托
Why don't you just tell Bree what you need?
你为什么不干脆告诉Bree你的需要？
Tell her what you want.
告诉她你想要什么
Because she'd say no.
因为她会说不
So? I've said no to some things you've asked me to do.
是吗？我也对你提出的一些要求说不了啊
Yeah, that's different.
是啊，但那不同
I don't care if you reject me.
如果你拒绝了，我不会介意
Rex...
do you trust me on this?
在这事上你信任我吗？
Sometimes when you love somebody,
有时候当你爱某人的时候，
you've just got to make sacrifices for them.
你必须要做出一些牺牲
Love or passion
爱情还是激情
-
it's an awful choice to make.
是一个很艰难的选择
Yes, it is.
是啊
Now, I have to warn you
现在，我必须警告你
-
this might hurt a little bit.
这可能会有点疼
Aah!
啊!
How am I supposed to live without a car?
没有车我怎么过日子啊
Okay, Gabrielle, listen. Tanaka's still at large, and they're going to want Carlos to flip on him,
Gabrielle,听我说，田中依然在逃， 警方希望Carlos把他供出来
so this is their way of playing hardball.
他们现在玩硬的了
Now, I'm guessing that they're not done yet.
我想这些还不算完
Why?
为什么？
What else could they take from us?
他们还能从我们这里拿走什么？
Pretty much anything.
几乎任何东西
It's all fair game if they even think they can trace it to ill-gotten gains.
如果他们认为这样做能追查到非法收入， 这将是一个很公平合理的方法。
No, no, no. No, some of this stuff is mine when I modeled, before I even met Carlos.
不行，不行，不行，不行，在遇到Carlos之前， 我曾是模特，这家里的一些东西都是我当年买的
See this?
看这个
Kosta boda. Bought it when I landed my first cover.
Kosta boda. 我第一次登上封面后买的
This
这个
- I spent eight hours on a rock in a bikini for that painting.
- 为了买这幅画我穿着比基尼 在一块岩石上呆了八个小时
I understand how you feel
我理解你的感受
-
no, you don't understand.
不，你不理解
I have dug myself up from dirt to afford these things,
我从逆境中起家，靠自己的努力买了这些东西，
and no one is going to take them away from me.
没有人可以从我身边拿走它们
Then I suggest you find yourself a good hiding place.
那么我建议你找一个好的隐藏地点
They can't take what they can't find.
他们只能拿走他们发现的东西
Oh, and if you can scare up that passport, too, that would be good.
哦，如果你能找到护照，那将会所有帮助
- Oh, hi, Gabrielle.
- 嗨，Gabrielle
Hi.
嗨
What have you got there?
你手里拿的是什么？
My china. I know how you've always loved it, and I thought you might want to borrow it for a while.
我的瓷器。我知道你一直很喜欢它， 我想也许你会想要借一阵子
Oh. Well, that's, um, very thoughtful of you.
嗯，你有心了
Say, um, can I store some odds and ends in your garage?
你看，我能不能放一些零碎的东西 在你的车库里？
Sure. Why don't you, uh, come by tomorrow?
当然，要不你明天来吧？
Sooner is better than later, right?
越早越好，对吧？
Oh.
Mm.
Aah.
Just like...
就像...
Come on now.
加油啊
Yes! Ah.
好! 啊
Rex?
Rex?!
I need an ambulance. Right away.
我需要一辆救护车，马上
Oh.
Hello?
你好?
Yes, this is she.
是的，是我
Yes, he's my husband.
是的，他是我丈夫
Um, excuse me. I'm here to see Rex Van De Kamp. Apparently, he had a heart attack.
嗯，不好意思，我来探望Rex Van De Kamp 他好像心脏病发作了
I'm not sure
我不确定
-
he's being prepped for surgery right now. If you'd like to wait...
他马上就要进手术室了 如果你想要等...
could I at least poke my head in? I'm his wife.
能不能让我至少看他一眼？我是他的妻子
You're his wife?
你是他的妻子？
Yes. Why?
是啊，怎么了？
I was thinking of a different patient.
我想我搞错病人了
Let me get the doctor.
我去找医生
[Rex Van De Kamp]
[Maisy Gibbons]
As Claire prepared for bed, she was unaware that somewhere else in the Scavo house,
当Claire准备上床睡觉的时候，她没有觉察到 在Scavo家的某个地方，
the day she had just finished was starting all over again.
她所度过的一天又重新开始了
The dog is blue, the doggie is blue
狗是蓝色的，小狗是蓝色的
Lynette was relieved to see that Claire was doing a good job.
看到Claire如此胜任她的工作， Lynette终于松了口气
But after further viewing...
但随着带子的播放...
come give me a 3-bear hug.
给我一个3熊抱
It dawned on Lynette...
Lynette渐渐觉得...
Claire might be doing her job a little too well.
Claire似乎做得过于好了一点
Here's the candles I borrowed.
这是我借用的蜡烛
Thanks.
谢谢
I'm trying to read, so if you don't mind...
我打算看会儿书，所以如果你不介意的话...
I cannot believe, after everything you did, you're mad at me.
我不敢相信，在你做了那些事之后， 你还生我的气
I told Zach that he could trust you, and you turned him in.
我告诉Zach他可以信任你， 可你却出卖了他
Yeah, well, someone had to be responsible, and like it or not,
总有人要负起责任，不管你喜欢与否，
I've got a birth certificate that says I'm your mother.
我始终是你的妈妈
Since when?
从什么时候开始的？
What is that supposed to mean?
你在说什么啊？
Since dad left, if there's been a mother around here, it's been me.
爸爸离开后，如果说有个妈妈在我身旁， 那就是我自己
Julie.
Julie
Do you remember after the divorce that you stayed in bed for a week and I had to beg you to eat something?
你还记得吗，离婚后你在床上躺了一礼拜 而我不得不求你吃些东西
Yeah, but
是啊，但是
-
and for weeks, I had to clean the house, I had to make sure that the bills were paid.
在接下来的数周里，我不得不打扫房子， 确保各种费用按时支付
I even had to schedule my own doctor's appointment once.
我有一次甚至不得不自己安排和医生的预约
I was in bad shape back then.
我那时候情况很糟
It's still going on.
目前依然是这样
And now that I need some support, you decide to play the mom card?
我现在需要支持， 而你却开始管教我了？
I had to send Zach back.
我必须把Zach送回去
We could have gotten in a lot of trouble.
不然我们可能会有很多的麻烦
Yeah, well, now Zach's the one who's in trouble.
是啊，不过，现在Zach有难了
You sent him back to a man who hates him.
你把他送回一个恨他的男人的身边
As gabrielle considered the vast emptiness of her new surroundings,
Gabrielle望着家中空荡荡的四周，
she was surprised to find there was only one thing she truly missed --
吃惊地发现只有一样东西是她真正想念的--
her husband.
她的丈夫
Mrs. Solis, we have a warrant to enter your house
Solis夫人，我们被授权进入你家
and repossess any goods which we suspect may have been obtained...illegally.
并且收回任何我们认为是非法所得的物品
We're not into clutter.
我想我们不会弄得乱七八糟的
All right,"harvey the flying turtle." Doesn't this look fun.
好，“Harvey：会飞的海龟”，这本看上去不错
Where's Claire?
Claire在哪儿？
I gave her the afternoon off.
我放了她下午假
Who wants to turn pages?
谁想来翻页？
Is she sick?
她生病了吗？
No, she's fine. I just wanted us all to spend the day together, you know?
不，她很好，我只是希望我们能一起度过这一天，
Like we used to. Here we go.
就像以前一样。开始吧
"Once upon a time, there was a young turtle named harvey.
“很久以前，有一只小海龟名叫Harvey”
"Every day, harvey would tell all the other turtles,
“Harvey每天都告诉其他海龟说，”
"'one day, I'm going to fly off this island "and go see the world.
“'有一天，我将飞离这个岛屿去看世界'”
'The other turtles laughed and said,'turtles can't fly.'"
“其它海龟笑着说，'海龟不会飞'”
Ooh, it's getting good now, huh?
哦，故事越来越精彩了，嗯？
W-what's wrong?
怎么了？
When Claire reads, she does funny voices.
Claire读故事的时候，她会发出好玩的声音
Does she, now?
是吗？
Okay.
好吧
"Harvey didn't like the turtles laughing, "so he told them,
“Harvey不喜欢海龟们笑话他，所以他对他们说，”
'I'll show you. One day I will fly higher than the birds.'"
'我会飞给你们看的，总有一天我会飞得比鸟都高'”
That's not funny.
不好玩
Yeah? Well, I'm just warming up.
是吗？嗯，我刚才只是热身而已
"Then bruno, the big, bad turtle, "took harvey up on the cliff and threw him over, "and he proclaimed,
“然后那个坏坏的大海龟Bruno说， 把Harvey带到悬崖上去并把他扔下去”
"'we'll see if you can fly. Fly or die, fly or die.'"
“到时候就知道你能不能飞了， 飞或者死，飞或者死”
When's Claire coming back?
Claire什么时候回来？
What happened to your nails?
你的指甲怎么了？
Oh, I -- I moved all our stuff to keep it from the feds.
哦，我把我们所有的东西都藏起来了， 这样联邦调查局的人就收不走了
It kills me that I'm putting you through this.
我真是对不起你，让你受了这些苦
Hands on the table.
把手放在桌子上
It's not your fault. You didn't do anything wrong.
这不是你的错，你没做错什么事
I'll take care of everything until you're back to do it yourself.
在你回来之前我会替你照看好所有东西的
And you will be soon.
你很快就能出来了
I got to be honest, I didn't know how you would hold up.
老实说，我不知道你是怎么坚持下来的
I knew you were a strong woman, but I had no idea.
我知道你是个坚强的女人，但我不知道
You're a good wife, gabby,
你是个好妻子，Gabby
a real partner.
一个真正的伙伴
Oh, Carlos, I love you so much.
哦，Carlos, 我非常地爱你
I would give up that house full of expensive junk just to put this behind us
我宁愿放弃那幢堆满了昂贵的废品的房子 来帮我们渡过这一关，
and have you home with me.
让你回到家中
That sounds pretty good right now.
听上去很不错
I'm going to kiss my husband now.
我要吻我的丈夫
Hands on the table.
把手放在桌上
There's a false panel on the back wall of my closet.
在我的衣柜的后墙上有个假的镶嵌板
My passport is there, along with some papers.
我的护照在那儿，还有其他一些文件
Take the passport to the lawyer and burn the papers.
把护照给律师，烧掉那些文件
Carlos, did you know what Tanaka was doing?
Carlos,你知道那个田中所做的事吗？
Just burn... the papers.
烧掉...那些文件
Hey, Lynette.
嗨，Lynette
Did Martha Huber happen to leave a spare key to her house with you?
Martha Huber有没有留了一把备用钥匙在你这儿？
No.
没有
Oh.
哦
Where is she, by the way? I haven't seen her in days.
顺便问一句，她在哪儿？我好几天没见她了
Got me.
我也不知道
She kicked me out so fast that I forgot my laptop,
她那么急着把我赶出来 以至于我忘了拿我的笔记本电脑
and there's just some stuff on there that I don't want anyone else to see.
那里面有一些东西我实在不想让别人看到
Oh. Well... good luck with that.
哦，嗯...祝你好运
You know, you're not looking half bad.
你知道吗，你看起来气色不错啊
What have you done with that little posse of yours?
你的那些孩子们怎么样了？
They're with the new nanny.
他们有了新的保姆
Wow, your own personal nanny? Smell you.
喔，你的私人保姆？不错啊
Well, trust me, it's not all it's cracked up to be.
相信我，那并不是像传闻中的那么好
You know, our mothers were smart.
我们的母亲们很聪明
They didn't get us nannies or put us in day care because they knew if they did, we'd find out
她们没有找保姆或把我们扔进日托所 是因为如果她们这么做了，我们会发现
there are other women out there who are better mothers than they were.
原来有比我们的妈妈更好的妈妈
You know, I had a nanny for a while growing up
其实我曾经有一个保姆
- Mrs. Muntz.
-Muntz夫人
You had a nanny?
你有过保姆？
Well, actually, she was more like a court-appointed social worker.
事实上，她更像是个法院指派的社工
My mom did a little time.
我妈妈在监狱里蹲了一阵子
She had a thing for bourbon and shoplifting.
她酗酒并且偷东西
Oh. Sorry.
哦，不好意思
Oh, Muntz was a hard-ass
Muntz很强硬
-no mercy.
-毫不留情
In fact, she was such a disciplinarian that when my mom made parole,
她是那么的厉行纪律， 以至于当我妈妈假释出来的时候
I was actually happy to see her.
我真的很高兴看到她
Really?
真的？
Yeah.
是啊
Lesser of two evils.
她是两个恶魔里相对好一点的那个
Huh.
嗯
Anyway, I got to find a key.
不管怎样，我必须找到房子钥匙
- See you later.
- 后见
Bye.
拜拜
Thanks for your help with Zach before.
谢谢你在Zach这事上帮了我的忙
Oh, it's my pleasure.
很荣幸
I hope he comes out of this okay.
希望他能顺利渡过这一切
He's a little squirrelly, but seems like a good kid.
他有点古怪，不过是个好孩子
Yeah.
是啊
So how's Julie taking all this?
Julie对这事的反应怎么样？
Not well.
不太好
She accused me of not being a good mother.
她说我不是一个好妈妈
Oh, you're a great mom.
你是个好妈妈
Well, she was sort of right.
也许她是对的
After my divorce, I really leaned on her a lot.
在离婚后，我经常依靠她
Seems natural.
就好像很自然的一样
And I still kind of do it.
我现在依然这样
I just want somebody to talk to about all my adult stuff, and she's right there,
我就是想找人说说我的那些成年人的事情， 而她就在我身边，
and she just acts so mature. I forget she's 13.
那么地成熟，以至于我忘了她只有13岁
Well, the good news is that from now on,
我想，有一个好消息，如果你从此以后
if you ever want to talk to somebody about grown-up stuff, you got me.
再想和谁说说成年人的事情，你可以来找我
Well, I can't talk to you about everything.
我不能和你说所有的话题啊
Oh.
是吗
What if I want to talk about the big crush I have on the plumber that lives across the street?
如果我想说的是我疯狂地爱上了住街对面的那个水管工， 那怎么办？
Big crush, huh?
疯狂爱上，嗯？
Oh, yeah.
是啊
Wow, you'd have to tell me more.
喔，你应该告诉我更多一些
Well, um... he's got a smile that's to die for,
嗯...他有迷死人的笑容
and don't get me started on his tattoo.
更不用说他的纹身
Thanks.
谢谢
Oh, Bree.
哦，Bree
What a-a nice surprise.
真是个惊喜啊
Would you like to come in?
进来坐吗？
Well, that depends.
那得看情况
Are you having an affair with my husband?
你是不是和我丈夫有一腿？
Would you like some more potatoes?
你想再要点土豆吗？
You already asked me that.
你已经说过了
Sorry.
不好意思
I'm so relieved you're safe, I'm, uh...
看到你平安无事我真是松了口气，我，嗯...
I'm not thinking straight.
我的想法有问题
Does that mean you're not going to send me back to silvercrest?
这么说你不会把我送回silvercrest了？
You've got to understand,
你必须明白
your behavior, the violence, breaking into the Van De Kamps'
你闯入Van De Kamp家的暴力行为
-
I just didn't know what you were going through.
我不知道你经历了些什么
You could have asked me.
你可以问我啊
Well...
我...
I've been remembering things...
我想起了一些事情...
things from when I was little.
我小时候的事情
What kind of things?
怎么样的事情？
Awful things.
不好的事情
Zach, listen to me.
Zach,听我说
Sometimes it's not good to look back on the past.
有时候不要想太多过去的事情
But I can't help it.
但我控制不了
These images just keep popping into my head.
那些影像不断地进入我的头脑
Well, then, you've got to find a way to push them back out again.
那么你应该找个办法把它们再赶出去
Okay.
好
More potatoes?
再来一些土豆？
Yes, please.
好的
Sure is nice to be back to normal.
回归正常绝对是件好事
You should know that Rex still loves you...
你应该知道Rex依然爱你...
very much.
非常爱你
He said that?
他那么说的？
Yes.
是的
Then why is he so unhappy?
那为什么他一直不高兴？
He has certain needs, and he's afraid to discuss them with you.
他有一些特殊的需要，他不敢和你说
Needs
需要
- like...
-比方说...
sexual needs?
性的需要？
Yes.
是的
And have you fulfilled those needs?
你满足了他的需要？
I see.
我明白了
You know, you are pretty brazen for a woman
作为女人，你真的很厚颜无耻
who just admitted, however tacitly, that she just slept with my husband.
尽管很隐晦，但你还是承认了和我丈夫有奸情
If I told anyone in this neighborhood, they would never speak to you again.
如果我告诉邻居们这个事情， 她们永远都不会和你说话了
You're not going to tell a soul.
你不会说的
Yeah, you may hate me, but you'd hate the humiliation a lot more.
你也许恨我，但你更憎恨被羞辱
Oh, I don't hate you, Maisy.
不，我不恨你，Maisy
I pity you.
我可怜你
Hi.
嗨
Oh, hey, Lynette. Are you heading out now?
嗨，Lynette.你现在就出发吗？
Yep.
是的
Um, I'll be home late, so just the usual routine
我可能会晚回来，所以就像往常一样
- a nap for penny, and
- 睡个觉给一便士，然后
-
I know, no sugar after 5:00. I got it.
我知道，下午五点以后不许吃糖，我明白
You're the best.
你是最好的
Oh, one more thing.
哦，还有一件事
Since the boys are having corn dogs for dinner,
因为孩子们晚饭吃玉米热狗，
I'd like you to make sure they get a vegetable to go with it.
我希望你能确保他们同时也吃一些蔬菜
Brussels sprouts?
芽甘蓝？
They're full of iron.
它们富含铁元素
Would you make sure they clean their plates?
你能保证他们全部吃光吗？
Not a problem.
没问题
I have this little trick I do. I cover the veggies with some cheese.
我有一个小窍门： 在蔬菜上浇一些奶酪
Ooh, you sly dog.
哦，你这个狡猾的家伙
That night, Lynette settled in to watch her personal pick for feel-good movie of the year.
那天晚上，Lynette观看了她认为是全年里最令她开心的电影
You guys, you need to eat your brussels sprouts.
伙计们，你们要把芽甘蓝都吃掉
Brussels sprouts!
芽甘蓝!
I don't want this!
我不想吃!
Hey! Yes, you do!
不，你想吃!
You guys, don't throw them
伙计们，不要把它们扔掉
- hey!
- 嗨!
Hey, stop it!
嗨，停下来!
Do not
不要
- ow! Hey! You guys, stop it!
- 噢! 嗨! 你们停下来!
Do not throw these at me, you guys! Cut it out!
你们别向我扔这些东西!停下来!
Hey.
嗨
I guess they operated, huh?
我猜已经动过手术了吧？
They sure did.
当然
How' d it go?
手术进行得怎么样？
It went well.
很顺利
The surgeon says you're going to be as good as new.
医生说会像全新的一样好
You look like you've been crying.
你看上去好像哭过
I have.
我是哭过
I was so afraid you were going to die.
我真害怕你会死
There's so many things I haven't had a chance to tell you.
有太多的事情我没有机会跟你说
I'm sorry you were so worried.
对不起，让你那么担心
It's okay.
没关系
How are you now, Rex?
Rex,你现在觉得怎么样？
Are you strong enough to listen to the things I need to tell you?
你能够听一听我想对你说的事情吗？
Sure, hon.
当然，甜心
I know you still love me.
我知道你依然爱我
Maisy told me.
Maisy告诉我的
She did?
她说了？
As of this moment, Rex,
在这个时候，Rex，
I am no longer your wife.
我不再是你的妻子
I am going to go out and find the most vindictive lawyer can find, and together, we are going to eviscerate you.
我会找一个最具报复性的律师， 和他一起，我们将掏空你的一切
I am going to take away your money,
我将拿走你的钱
your family,
你的家庭
and your dignity.
和你的尊严
Do you hear me?
你听到了吗？
Bree
-
and I am so thrilled to know that you still love me,
当我听到你说你还爱我的时候我还真是兴奋啊
because I want what's about to happen to you...
因为我希望即将发生在你身上的事...
to hurt as much as is humanly possible.
会最大程度地伤害你
I'm so glad you didn't die before I got a chance to tell you that.
我真高兴你活着听我讲完了这些话
Trust is a fragile thing.
信任真是一件脆弱的东西
Bye, guys.
再见，伙计们
- Bye, mom. Bye, mom.
- 拜拜，妈妈
Bye, mommy.
拜拜，妈妈
Once earned, it affords us tremendous freedom.
一旦赢得了，会提供给我们巨大的空间
But once trust is lost, it can be impossible to recover.
而一旦失去了，就不可能再恢复了
[SOLOMON, MILLER & HAAS FAMILY LAW]
[SOLOMON, MILLER & HAAS家庭法律事务所]
Of course, the truth is
当然，事实上
we never know who we can trust.
我们永远不知道我们能信任谁
Those we're closest to can betray us.
那些我们最亲近的人可能会背叛我们
Police. Open up.
警察，开门
And total strangers can come to our rescue.
而陌生人却能帮助我们
In the end,
到头来，
most people decide to trust only themselves.
大多数人决定只信任他们自己
It really is the simplest way
这的确是简单的方法